Zac Heisey

Full Stack Marketer

Baltimore, MD

Mobile: (408) 444-0546 | Email: zheisey@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/zacheisey

Portfolio: http://www.zac-heisey.com AngelList: https://angel.co/zac-heisey

Objective

To contribute in a leadership role, leveraging 9+ years of experience in digital marketing, content creation, project management, research, analysis, design, and web development. My ultimate goal is to earn a VP of Marketing or CMO position with a growing startup.

Experience

Optimization Strategist - Showroom Logic - Remote

May 2016 - Present

• Responsible for management and optimization of ~200 paid search marketing accounts, including budget management, ad testing, keyword research, reporting, and analysis.

Co-Founder - Tribe Interactive, LLC - Bay Area, CA

May 2014 - Dec. 2015

- As Director of Digital marketing, oversaw all areas of digital marketing including PPC, SEO, social media, display, email, retargeting, content creation, and conversion rate optimization (CRO).
- Developed end-to-end strategies across multiple marketing channels.
- Managed team of content creators, designers, and other digital specialists.
- Cultivated strategic partnerships with vendors, advertising partners, etc.
- Utilized an array of marketing automation, research, analytics, testing, and tracking tools to increase traffic, conversions, and increase overall performance.

Paid Search Manager - BRIM Agency - San Diego, CA

Jan. 2014 - Sep. 2014

• Audited, optimized, and managed paid search campaigns across multiple online advertising platforms (Google, Bing, Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, etc.).

Director of Paid Search - AdChoice, Inc. - San Diego, CA

Feb. 2012 - Dec. 2013

 Worked directly with CEO to develop internal paid search methodology and lead end-toend management of all paid search campaigns.

Senior Account Manager - Best Rank, Inc. - San Diego, CA

Nov. 2007 - Feb. 2012

 Served as day-to-day contact for SEO and PPC clients, driving all aspects of online marketing strategy.

Education

Nebraska Wesleyan University - Lincoln, NE

2003-2007

- B.A. Communication | Minor, Public Relations
- Lamda Pi Eta member (National Communication Honor Society)